[
    {
        "question": "Secure your Crypto!",
        "answer": "BEST PROJECT EVER"
    },
    {
        "question": "Forks Explained",
        "answer": "Go Get"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ton voices live",
        "answer": "I LOVE BLUM"
    },
    {
        "question": "How to Analyze Crypto?",
        "answer": "VALUE"
    },
    {
        "question": "Navigating Crypto",
        "answer": "HEYBLUM"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are Telegram Mini Apps?",
        "answer": "CRYPTOBLUM"
    },
    {
        "question": "Say No to Rug Pull!",
        "answer": "SUPERBLUM"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Are AMMs?",
        "answer": "CryptoSmart"
    },
    {
        "question": "Liquidity Pools Guide",
        "answer": "BLUMERSSS"
    },
    {
        "question": "$2.5M+ DOGS Airdrop",
        "answer": "HAPPYDOGS"
    },
    {
        "question": "Doxxing? What's that?",
        "answer": "NODOXXING"
    },
    {
        "question": "Pre-Market Trading?",
        "answer": "WOWBLUM"
    },
    {
        "question": "Play track & type track name",
        "answer": "Blum - Big City Life"
    },
    {
        "question": "How To Memecoin?",
        "answer": "Memeblum"
    },
    {
        "question": "Token Burning: How & Why?",
        "answer": "Onfire"
    },
    {
        "question": "Crypto Terms. Part 1?",
        "answer": "Blumexplorer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bitcoin Rainbow Chart?",
        "answer": "soblum"
    },
    {
        "question": "How to trade Perps?",
        "answer": "CRYPTOFAN"
    },
    {
        "question": "How To Find Altcoins?",
        "answer": "ULTRABLUM"
    },
    {
        "question": "DeFi Explained",
        "answer": "Blumforce"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sharding Explained",
        "answer": "Blumtastic"
    },
    {
        "question": "Crypto Slang. Part 1",
        "answer": "BLUMSTORM"
    },
    {
        "question": "Pumptober Special",
        "answer": "PUMPIT"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is On-chain Analysis?",
        "answer": "BLUMEXTRA"
    },
    {
        "question": "DeFi Risks: Key Insights",
        "answer": "BLUMHELPS"
    },
    {
        "question": "Choosing a Crypto Exchange",
        "answer": "CRYPTOZONE"
    },
    {
        "question": "Crypto Slang. Part 2",
        "answer": "FOMOOO"
    },
    {
        "question": "DeFi Risks: Key Insights",
        "answer": "BLUMHELPS"
    },
    {
        "question": "Understanding Gas Fees",
        "answer": "CRYPTOGAS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Slippage?",
        "answer": "Cryptobuzz"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's Crypto DEX?",
        "answer": "Dexxx"
    },
    {
        "question": "Node Sales in Crypto",
        "answer": "BLUMIFY"
    },
    {
        "question": "Crypto Terms. Part 1",
        "answer": "BLUMEXPLORER"
    },
    {
        "question": "How to Memecoin?",
        "answer": "memeblum"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Staking?",
        "answer": "VALUE"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whatâ€™s Next for DeFi?",
        "answer": "BLUMNOW"
    },
    {
        "question": "Smart Scontracts 101",
        "answer": "SMARTBLUM"
    },
    {
        "question": "DEX History",
        "answer": "GODEX"
    },
    {
        "question": "Regulation: Yay or Nay?",
        "answer": "BLUMSSS"
    },
    {
        "question": "Crypto Slang. Part 3",
        "answer": "BOOBLUM"
    },
    {
        "question": "Smart Contracts 101",
        "answer": "SMARTBLUM"
    },
    {
        "question": "P2P Trading Safety Tips",
        "answer": "BLUMTIPS"
    },
    {
        "question": "Crypto Regulations #2",
        "answer": "Blumrules"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is Binance a DEX?",
        "answer": "BLUMIES"
    },
    {
        "question": "Crypto Communities",
        "answer": "BLUMMUNITY"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dec 6 Crypto News",
        "answer": "HUNDRED"
    },
    {
        "question": "DEX Evolution",
        "answer": "BLUMSPARK"
    },
    {
        "question": "Crypto Slang. Part 4",
        "answer": "LAMBOBLUM"
    },
    {
        "question": "Memepad Tutorial",
        "answer": "Memepad"
    },
    {
        "question": "DEX History #3",
        "answer": "LOVEBLUM"
    }
]